

054-2609225 <u>itzikil@icloud.com</u>

Full-stack Developer https://github.com/ltzikil

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer with experience in writing single-page applications using the latest WEB technologies (Vue.js, Vuex, Node.js, React.js, Redux, Angular, etc.).

Graduate of the Coding Academy – 640 hours of an intensive coding bootcamp that qualifies Full-Stack developers.

My latest work: Fiverr clone (Vue.js, Node.js, MongoDB):

https://gigerr.onrender.com/

Tech skills

- MVC Frameworks, single-page applications (SPAs) and PWA using Vue.js, React and Angular.
- Server-side programming, APIs and REST with Node.js.
- Modern JavaScript (ES6) including Object Oriented Programing.
- HTML5, CSS3 and SASS.
- MongoDB.
- Basic knowledge in php, jQuery, MySQL.
- Other technologies Tailwind, Bootstrap, Vite, Express, Git.

Professional Experience

2020-present Musician – recording and performance

2021-2022	Music teacher –	aroups and	private lessons
-----------	-----------------	------------	-----------------

2018-2021 Backliner – building and operating stages at music concerts

2018-2021 "Impact" scholarship – volunteering in food distribution

2015-2017 Army service – at command post of battalion commander at Givati

Education

2022-2023	Full-Stack Web Co	ding Bootcamp	Coding Academy
LULL LULJ	I dii Stack vvcb co	anna boottanna.	Codina Academy

2018-2022 Music school, Mizmor, Givat Washington

2012-2018 Yeshiva, Itamar

Other Interests Sports, music, new technologies.

Qualities Autodidact, self-discipline, curiosity, perceptiveness.

Other Programs Cubase and DaVinci Resolve.

Languages Hebrew - mother-tongue, English – fluent.